let questions = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "Which technology is used to create immersive experiences in Virtual Reality?",
      answer: "3D Graphics",
      options: [
        "2D Graphics",
        "3D Graphics",
        "Text-based Interfaces",
        "Virtual Assistants"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "Which JavaScript library is commonly used for creating VR experiences?",
      answer: "A-Frame",
      options: [
        "React",
        "Angular",
        "Vue.js",
        "A-Frame"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "What is the term used to describe the spatial audio technique in VR?",
      answer: "3D Audio",
      options: [
        "Surround Sound",
        "Stereo Audio",
        "3D Audio",
        "Monaural Sound"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "Which of the following devices is NOT commonly used for VR experiences?",
      answer: "Smartwatch",
      options: [
        "Oculus Rift",
        "HTC Vive",
        "PlayStation VR",
        "Smartwatch"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "What is the purpose of head tracking in VR?",
      answer: "To adjust the perspective based on the user's head movements",
      options: [
        "To track eye movements",
        "To measure heart rate",
        "To adjust the brightness of the display",
        "To adjust the perspective based on the user's head movements"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "Which of the following is NOT a component of a VR headset?",
      answer: "Touchscreen Display",
      options: [
        "Display",
        "Lenses",
        "Motion Sensors",
        "Touchscreen Display"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "What is WebVR?",
      answer: "An API that provides access to VR devices through the web browser",
      options: [
        "A VR headset manufacturer",
        "A VR game development platform",
        "A VR content marketplace",
        "An API that provides access to VR devices through the web browser"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "Which of the following is NOT a method for controlling VR experiences?",
      answer: "Taste",
      options: [
        "Gaze-based Interaction",
        "Hand Gestures",
        "Voice Commands",
        "Taste"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "What is the term used to describe the sensation of dizziness or nausea in VR?",
      answer: "Simulator Sickness",
      options: [
        "Virtual Vertigo",
        "VR Nausea",
        "Simulation Sickness",
        "Simulator Sickness"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "Which of the following is an example of a VR application?",
      answer: "Virtual Tour of a Museum",
      options: [
        "Text-based Adventure Game",
        "Social Media Platform",
        "E-commerce Website",
        "Virtual Tour of a Museum"
      ]
    }
  ];
  